KISHAN CHAUHAN

HEAD OF CONTENT / WRITER / CONTENT STRATEGIST / EDITOR

783 825 0037

kisc106@gmail.com

kishnn.com

Proficient writer-editor-strategist with years of experience in researching, formulating content to drive **brand image**, construct web and social media strategy to **generate leads**, and manage teams to optimum **levels of productivity**. Works with minimal input to produce engaging, authoritative and error-free work.

EXPERIENCE

HEAD OF CONTENT

Appventurez Mobitech

12/2022 - Present

Handled a team of writers and graphic designers in producing exemplary content and upscale DA. Collaborated with clients to develop marketable content for product ad-campaigns.

SENIOR CONTENT STRATEGIST

Appventurez Mobitech

08/2022 - 12/2022

Wrote in-house blogs, GPs, and featured posts to maximize outreach and build site authority to generate relevant leads. Strategized content for official site and Linkedin to refine brand image.

DEPUTY MANAGING EDITOR

Aglasem Edutech

08/2021 - 08/2022

Led a team of writers in producing 40+ news stories on a routine basis. Additionally, headed Aglasem's collaboration with Indian Express for the delivery of education-based stories.

COLUMN WRITER & CORRESPONDENT

The Colloguy Youth Media

09/2019 - 07/2021

Wrote and formulated new articles primarily on events in the tech space and implications on geopolitics and the domestic digital infrastructure.

EDUCATION



Bachelor of Arts (Hons.) in History

Ramjas College, University of Delhi 2017 - 2020



Certificate in Creative WritingBritish Council, New Delhi

2016

FREELANCE EXPERIENCE

CONTENT DEVELOPER

Testbook Edu Solutions

01/2022 - 08/2022

Writing and editing sets of articles on education and career opportunities in the public sphere and the government sector.